I'm going to make a very bold claim.
These two apps I'm about to show you have
saved me about 10 hours a week.
They made me a better thinker,
a better creator,
and come up with better ideas.
And quite honestly,
I couldn't imagine running a business
without them.
Now one of them you will have heard of,
this one here,
but I can't believe how many
of you still haven't heard of this one
right here.
Now,
the magic isn't either of them on their
own.
The magic is when you combine them
together.
This introduction right now
was even curated from mixing the two,
and I just read
it out word for word, and I thought,
"That is a good hook." Introducing an app
called Whisperflow.
Now imagine a world where you talk to your
computer or your
phone, similar to the dictate feature,
but it's a lot more accurate.
Now some of us are already doing this
within our life, but you often can't speak
for more than 30 or 40 seconds before you
have to go back and check, and then
there's a blatant, obvious mistake,
and it's going to ruin absolutely
everything
else that's happened from that.
Whisperflow changes that.
Now,
I've actually been very hesitant to make
AI content because I don't think it's
as impressive as everyone makes out on the
internet.
But this is a tool
that doesn't do your work for you.
It enables you to get more work done.
Speaking is roughly three times faster
than any amount of written or typed
words or verbiage that you can do.
If you can speak 150 words into Claude
instead of typing 40 or 50,
that's going to make a massive impact.
Not to mention, when I'm ideating,
often I need to be on the move, not at my
computer.
Come up with my best ideas in the shower,
when I'm on a dog walk, or
sometimes even right here in my office,
if I'm with a member of staff,
I'm sat back
on my chair firing ideas. What
if we did this? What if we did this?
What if we did this?
Using this software
is enabling me to use my
brain better. Another thing
is sometimes we really overestimate how
good our memory
is at remembering things.
So we have an idea, we go,
"I'll type it down in a
minute." Or our phone's not available to
us, or we're currently doing something
else, so we're changing an app. With this,
I can open the notes section on my
phone, tap into Whisperflow,
and I'm going to show you how to install
it in a
second, and I can just talk for five, six,
seven minutes, and I know it's going to
get everything that I want.
It's like an assistant on tap.
But one of the most powerful things
is I can think out loud
and actually come to
the conclusions and the ideas
that I want to whilst doing other tasks,
even whilst
driving.
And I'm not sure of the legality of me
saying that.
So just before I get into even more
reasons as to why this is an incredibly
powerful tool,
let me show you how to install it.
So download the app,
you get to use it for free.
Drag it into the applications folder.
It's going to ask you some annoying
questions. Cool.
Just have to set up some permissions here.
Boom.
Now I'm probably going to upgrade to the
pro shortly. But let's give this a go.
So now if I want to do hands-free,
which I often do,
I'm going to press function
and space bar. My name's James Smith.
I'm a YouTuber.
I run several YouTube accounts. However,
this one that I'm working on is designed
for business owners, solopreneurs,
and I want you to help me
ideate some things
that I could help them with.
So there are probably three segments in
which I would say I'm an expert
or I've got
a lot of experience.
It would be to do with content,
to do with leads, and to do
with making money. So let's look at
that first segment to begin with.
So as far as content creation,
I believe that a lot of people watching
these videos
probably have their iPhones.
They might think they need more equipment.
They may be a bit paralyzed to the fact
that that's the reason why they're not
making content.
They know they need to pick up their phone
and shoot.
They're not sure
which platforms to edit in.
They're not really sure what to talk about
as well because they're not
self-obsessed.
They don't feel the need to wake up
and talk about themselves all
day.
So if you could give me seven different
content ideas that I could put out,
all I need is the titles,
and I can run with it because I'm fairly
experienced in
this. Now as far as leads, I think
that people sometimes think they need to
get
clients from social media.
They think they need to get sales from
social media, and
they completely overlook the fact
that they, in fact,
should be getting leads.
So seven different content ideas
surrounding how to get more leads,
whether it's lead magnets,
whether it's why we need leads,
how many of your
followers should be leads, et cetera,
good quality leads.
I'll leave that for you to think about.
Then the making money thing.
I think that because most of my audience
is Australian, British, the whole idea
of talking about making money is uncouth,
and I think that a lot of the time it
can seem like a dirty word.
So let's frame it around maybe
commodities,
making money as raising prices, different
ticket prices, high ticket, low ticket,
how to scale, all of those kind of
things. So what I need from you
is to segment.
Let's do seven pieces of content for each
one of those.
Yeah, just give me some titles,
things to run with,
because right now I've got a
blank slate, blank afternoon,
and I need to promote a three-day free
event that I'm
doing called Content Leads Money.
So in that,
could you please just remind me to put a
call to action in there so
that I could say to them,
there's a link in the description.
Come to Content Leads Money,
three-day event, going to be doing it,
and that they
should register because it's free.
Inception.
And yeah,
so that's really what I need from you
right now.
Also, from all of this, I understand
that I'm giving you quite a lot of
information,
a lot of things to think about.
If you have any questions for me,
I'm happy for you to ask me
if you think it could
help you create me a better answer.
Now,
I know this looks like a scary amount of
text.
If I want it to break up the text,
I can just say line break.
And that's what I do
when I'm using it on the move to do
LinkedIn posts, which I've
started doing whilst walking a pram.
So I've got a dog, pram, child, phone.
I'm putting out posts,
putting out LinkedIn posts,
putting out ideas, ideating.
That's what this has done for me.
Some of my friends don't even know I'm
doing
this, but let's hit it. Now,
one of the most beautiful thing here
is it's doing
this for me, which is great. So often
when AI gives us some ideation,
I'm just going to go through that now.
I'm going to do the same thing again.
Oh, by the way, Nutonic
is now in Sainsbury's as part of the meal
deal, so
jump in there. Function space. Okay,
looking through these now. Looks good.
Your iPhone is good enough.
Stop waiting and start posting.
Now, I don't think this is good enough.
I think we should be saying to people how
to get leads from your iPhone, how to
establish a voice.
Let's talk about becoming a brand,
becoming a household name
using your iPhone. No, stop waiting
and start posting.
Bit too motivational for me.
The second one,
you don't have to talk about yourself to
make great content.
Again I think this could even just be,
"How to make great content without talking
about yourself." The third one,
"The only three things your audience
actually wants
to hear from you." I don't really think
that's strong enough.
Number four,
"Why nobody cares what camera you're
using." I think that actually
jumps into number one.
I would have thought you,
being super knowledgeable, that
you might explain about hooks
and setups and payoffs.
So maybe let's do that again.
Number five,
"How to find 30 content ideas in 30
minutes without leaving your
desk." That should be shorter, I think,
because if this was a YouTube title, "How
to come up with content ideas." Number
six, "The one editing app you need and
nothing else." Maybe we talk about why
Instagram edits will get you ahead.
Why Instagram edits killed CapCut.
The interesting death of CapCut.
How Instagram edits changed the game.
These are things
that I would've thought would've made good
hooks.
You could say, "Instagram edits
is here in CapCut.
Instead, let me explain why."
And number seven,
"Which platform should you post on
first?" Again,
I don't think that's very strong.
So what I want from you to do
is to go through all of these again with
my
feedback and completely change all of
those. Is that clear?
The interesting thing here as well is,
as I'm explaining all of this and putting
stuff across, the AI, Claude,
is getting to learn
and understand this kind
of ideation. And the thing is here,
the caveat here is,
I'm not getting AI to do my
work for me.
I'm helping AI take the ideas from my
brain, because
everything I need to make money,
scale my business, do better,
grow online is in
here, and it's the same for you.
What we're doing here
is we're extracting that and
we're organizing that.
I can do a seven-hour business talk in
front of 1,000
people. The slides aren't for things
that I forget.
It's to keep the structure of what I'm
saying.
All of you watching this
are experts in your own places.
We utilize tools like this to get it out
of where we are.
Okay, I think these are okay.
I probably would spend a bit more time
here.
So that is Whisperflow on the desktop.
Okay, so Whisperflow, again,
works on mobile, as you can see here.
You can see I was even talking on the way
here, giving it ideas.
So how this works
when you're in a WhatsApp is,
here's me chatting to Tesh, my
barber. Now,
it integrates into the keyboard.
So what I'm going to do
is I'm going to press in the bottom left,
and what's going
to come up is it's going to say Start
Flow. So I press Start Flow.
It jumps to the app, but I can swipe back.
"Thank you so much, mate.
I do apologize in advance that my son
is going to scream the building down as we
give him a haircut." Line break,
line break.
"Just want to say I appreciate you as a
barber, and I know it's been emotional.
We've had to shave my head because I'm
going bald." Line break, line break.
"But it's been a great ride of you holding
onto my hairline
for so long,
and I think now it's just time
that we let it go." Line break, line
break. ♪Let it go,
let it go♪ You get the message.
Appreciate you. And that
is just nicely out there.
Okay,
I'm not actually going to send him that.
But again, so we are,
from a business perspective, sure, this is
great.
But if we think about it from day to day,
we're saving time.
Less time on our phone,
more time interacting with people,
more messages, getting
emails done. On the walks, AirPods in,
out and about, getting
stuff sent to people. Because voice notes,
people hate receiving them, sending them
isn't great. The text to speech, not
that accurate. This opens up a new world.
So suddenly cooking, walking, driving
are all times for you to sit there and go,
"Hey,
what kind of things could we do for this?
What kind of things could we do for that?
What should I be looking on?" Again,
there are other things.
We can put transcripts into Claude from
other competitors
on YouTube and say, "Hey, these
are the three top videos in my niche.
Here's the existing script that I've got.
I'm thinking that somehow we take the
evidence from this, we do this,
we do this,
we do this.
What do you think?" You could think for
writing a book.
You could talk to your computer.
You could ideate.
You could even write a bloody book using
Whisperflow.
But better yet,
we get to claw back time from other areas,
whether it's emails.
"Hey, John, sorry about that. Look,
really would love to get some time to sit
down.
Diary's looking pretty hectic."
That three minutes responding to this
email becomes
one minute, and that time
that we're squeezing in
is more time we could put into
ideation,
more time we could put into prompting,
more time we could get into
discussing AI. We
are getting to squeeze other tasks
that couldn't have been done
before and putting our time into other
places we get compounding returns,
like this
video. But the best thing here
is so many of us have been asking AI to
produce scripts for us,
and they sound robotic.
They sound predictable.
They don't sound human. Now,
we can use the human
component and put
that into AI so we get the written version
what we've wanted all
along, but it sounds like us.
If you're not using these two things, I
suggest that you put them together.
I'm not the biggest fan of AI.
I'm not the biggest fan of people online
using it to get views and clout and to
hype up things just to grow their email
list.
But these two, I think,
can put you ahead of other people,
and there is going to be
a golden era before everyone
is using this.
I actually foresee, mark my words,
that WhatsApp will probably
purchase Whisperflow.
How sure am I of that?
Well, I don't know, but it makes sense.
So chuck those two things in
and please do register for my free
three-day event
coming up,
where we're going to be going through
content leads and money.
It's going to be live,
it's going to be super interactive,
going to be super fun.
So I'll see you there. Enjoy the apps.
I'll put links to them in description.
And if you enjoyed this video,
you're going to absolutely love this one
right here.